<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Patriotism</string>
    <string name="independence">72 years of Independence</string>
    <string name="memory">In the loving memory of our brave freedom fighters.</string>
    <string name="quote">One individual may die for an idea, but that idea will after his death, incarnate itself in a thousand lives</string>

    <string-array name="aboutThisDay">
        <item>The date, 15th of August from 1947 in India has become a</item>
        <item>very important day in the Indian history. It was the luckiest</item>
        <item>day of year 1947 when India became independent after</item>
        <item>lots of hard struggle and sacrifices of the Indian freedom</item>
        <item>fighters. We won freedom after a hard struggle. When India</item>
        <item>got its independence, the public of India had chosen their</item>
        <item>first Prime Minister, Pundit Jawaharlal Nehru who had</item>
        <item>unfurled the tricolour National Flag at the Red Fort in the</item>
        <item>national capital, New Delhi for the first time. All the people</item>
        <item>rejoice this special day with great joy every year.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>Long years ago, we made a tryst with destiny and now the time comes
when we shall redeem our pledge… At the stroke of the midnight hour,
when the world sleeps, India will awake to life and freedom. –
Jawaharlal Nehru</item>

        <item>So long as you do not achieve social liberty, whatever freedom is
provided by the law is of no avail to you…
B.R. Ambedkar</item>

        <item>India is a country in which every great religion finds a home.
Anni Besant</item>

        <item>Don’t see others doing better than you, beat your own records
everyday, because success is a fight between you and yourself.
Chandra Shekhar Azad</item>

        <item>Patriotism is religion and religion is love for India. Bankim Chandra  Chatterjee</item>

        <item>If yet your blood does not rage, then it is water that flows in your
veins. For what is the flush of youth, if it is not of service to the
motherland. – Chandra Shekhar Azad</item>

        <item>There is no dream, and if there is, there is only one to see you my
children struggling for the same and for which I am expected to be
finished.
Ashfaqulla Khan</item>

        <item>The sanctity of law can be maintained only so long as it is the
expression of the will of the people.
Bhagat Singh</item>

        <item>First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win.
Mahatma Gandhi</item>

        <item>In attaining our ideals, our means should be as pure as the end
Dr. Rajendra Prasad</item>

        <item>The shots that hit me are the last nails to the coffin of British rule in India.
Lala Lajpat Rai.</item>

        <item>An eye for an only ends up making the whole world blind.
Mahatma Gandhi</item>

        <item>Swaraj is my birth right and I shall have it.
Bal Gangadhar Tilak</item>

        <item>A country’s greatness lies in its undying ideals of love and sacrifice that inspire the mothers of the race.
Sarojini Naidu</item>

        <item>‘We believe in peace and peaceful development, not only for ourselves but for people all over the world.
Lal Bahadur Shastri</item>

        <item>Life should be great rather than long.
B. R. Ambedkar</item>

        <item>Give me blood and I will give you freedom.
Subhash Chandra Bose</item>

        <item>Bombs and pistols do not make a revolution. The sword of revolution is sharpened on the whetting-stone of ideas.
Bhagat Singh</item>

        <item>Every Indian should now forget that he is a Rajput, a Sikh or a Jat. He must remember that he is an Indian.
Sardar Patel</item>

        <item>You have to dream before your dreams can come true.
Maulana Abul Kalam Azad</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
